Episode 5: Wishing You All the Lies in the World
(麻衣)ふ～ん 事情はわかったわ｡
女子高生って大変ね｡
I get the gist of it.
High school girls have it rough, huh?
That's all you have to say?
(咲太)それだけ？
If I scolded you, it'd only make you happy.
私が叱ると 咲太 喜ぶじゃない｡
咲太の場合 罰を与えないほうが
罰になるみたいだし｡
In your case, not punishing you
is punishment enough.
でも なんか釈然としない｡
But something doesn't add up here.
Pretending to be a couple should be one of the things you hate most.
恋人のふりなんてｳｿ
咲太 嫌いでしょ？
こんなｳｿ 好きなやつ
いないと思うけど｡
I don't think anyone likes lying like this.
だから 釈然としないの｡
That's why it doesn't add up.
What are you hiding from me?
何を隠してるのよ？
実は さっきから
Well, I've been staring at your legs and getting aroused for a while.
麻衣さんの足見て 興奮してる｡
そ それは知ってるわよ｡
I-I know that.
ﾊｧ… いいから さっさと
白状しなさい｡
Spill the beans already.
古賀のやつ
Koga used the same words Kaede did when she stopped going to school.
かえでが不登校になったときと
同じこと言ったんですよ｡
恥ずかしいって｡
"Shameful." "Ashamed."
前沢先輩に告白されたことが
友達にﾊﾞﾚたら
If her friends learned that
Maesawa-senpai asked her out,
ｸﾗｽに居場所がなくなるって｡
she'd become an outcast in class.
No Members
Yep, see you tomorrow!
And that she'd be ashamed if people saw her as someone with no friends.
No Members
Yep, see you tomorrow!
Today
ひとりぼっちだと思われるのは
恥ずかしいから嫌だって｡
No Members
Yep, see you tomorrow!
Today
Rena has left the chat.
No Members
Yep, see you tomorrow!
Today
Rena has left the chat.
No Members
Yep, see you tomorrow!
Today
Rena has left the chat.
No Members
Yep, see you tomorrow!
Today
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
No Members
Today
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
No Members
Today
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
No Members
Today
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
No Members
Today
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
No Members
Rena has left the chat.
Aya has left the chat.
Hinako has left the chat.
つまらない｡
Boring.
Hey, I gave you a straight answer.
まじめな話をしたら それ？
Now that you've brought up your sister, I can't complain.
妹さんのことを持ち出されたら
文句なんて言えない｡
I'll overlook it, just this time.
今回だけは大目に見てあげる｡
ありがとうございます！
でも そうね
Thank you so much!
But, well...
ただ許すのも
今後のためにならないから
Simply allowing it would set a bad precedent,
相応の誠意を見せなさい｡
so show me some sincerity.
何をしろと？
And how do I do that?
それくらい自分で考えなさいよ｡
Figure that out yourself.
じゃあ…｡
ちょっ なに!?
Then...
Wait, what?
To show my sincerity.
だから誠意を…｡
それは性欲！
That's just your sexuality!
じゃ じゃあ ﾃﾞｰﾄは？
Th-Then how about a date?
来週の日曜日 鎌倉へ
あじさいを見に…｡
We can go see the hydrangeas in Kamakura
this coming Sund—
あっ！
明日から１週間
I'm away for a week from tomorrow. TV shoot in Kagoshima.
ﾄﾞﾗﾏの撮影で鹿児島｡
いいなぁ 鹿児島｡
遊びにいくんじゃないのよ｡
Wow, I wanna go to Kagoshima too.
I'm not going there to have fun.
そうだ これ あげる｡
Oh, right.
Take this.
They let me have the outfit I modeled for a fashion magazine shoot.
ﾌｧｯｼｮﾝ雑誌の撮影で使った衣装を
もらったから｡
鹿児島に行ってる間 これを
麻衣さんの代わりだと思えと？
You want me to think of this as you while you're away in Kagoshima?
It's for your sister!
妹さんによ！
She's fifteen this year, isn't she?
今年で15歳でしょ？
おしゃれをしたら
I thought that maybe dressing up
would make her want to go outside a little.
ちょっとは外に出てみたいって
気持ちに なるかもしれないし｡
Wh-What?
な 何よ？
I'm just so happy that you're thinking about Kaede.
麻衣さんが かえでのこと
考えてくれてるのが うれしくて｡
かえで呼んできます｡
Let me go get her.
あ？ 何してるんだ？
What are you doing?
I-It's not what you think!
I wasn't playing ninja or anything!
ち 違います 忍者ごっこを
していたわけではありません｡
I thought you were eavesdropping, actually.
僕は盗み聞きをしてたのかと
思ったんだが｡
まっ ちょうどいい｡
え？
Well, you saved me the trouble.
Good evening.
こんばんは｡
こ こんばんは…｡
G-Good evening.
これ 麻衣さんから｡
Mai-san brought this for you.
着てみたら？
Why not try it on?
Yes, you look very cute.
うん かわいい｡
I've never dressed up like this before.
I'm a little embarrassed.
こんなの初めてだから
恥ずかしいです｡
Don't forget to thank Mai-san.
麻衣さんに お礼言わないとな｡
あ ありがとうございます｡
Oh, thank you so much!
どういたしまして｡
You're very welcome.
あ あの…｡
何？
U-Um...
What?
かえでも 麻衣さんって
呼んでいいですか？
May I call you Mai-san too?
いいわよ｡
Of course. And I'll call you Kaede-chan, okay?
私も かえでちゃんって呼ぶね｡
は はい！
Sure!
Thank you very much for tonight.
今日は ありがとうございました｡
何よ 改まって｡
Why so formal?
かえでが 僕以外の人としゃべるの
久しぶりなんですよ｡
It's been ages since Kaede's talked so much
with anyone other than me.
ずっと引きこもってたから｡
After all, she hasn't set foot outside in ages.
咲太が そう素直だと
いじりがいがな～い｡
I can't mess with you when you're so upfront.
I just hope that lie doesn't turn into the truth.
ふりが本気にならなきゃいいけど｡
何？
What?
あの１年生のことよ｡
I'm talking about that first-year.
明日は ﾊﾞｲﾄのあとﾃﾞｰﾄなんでしょ？
You're going on a date after work tomorrow, right?
僕は麻衣さん一筋なので
大丈夫です｡
Don't worry. I only have eyes for you, Mai-san.
If you don't get it, then never mind.
わかってないなら いい｡
え？
おやすみ｡
おやすみなさい…｡
Night.
Good night.
June 29th
Kunimi.
国見 ﾊﾞｽｹ部に
前沢って先輩いるよな？
You have a Maesawa on your basketball team, right?
Hmm? Oh, you mean Yousuke-senpai?
(国見)ん？ ああ 陽介先輩な｡
どんな人だ？
What's he like?
どんな人って…｡
Well, he's the best baller in our school.
まっ うちの学校じゃ
いちばんﾊﾞｽｹうまいな｡
そんでもって かなりﾓﾃる｡
その調子で
And he's pretty popular with the ladies.
Keep going. Give me more info that'll make me hate him.
もっと嫌いになれそうな
情報をくれ｡
なんだよ それ｡
説明しにくいんだが…｡
What the heck?
It's hard to explain, but it'll hurt my conscience if he's a nice guy.
いい人だと 僕の良心が痛む｡
Well, I don't like badmouthing people,
まっ あんま人のこと
悪く言いたかないけど
昨日の部活帰りに 今の彼女が
全然やらせてくんないから
but yesterday after practice,
he said his girlfriend wasn't putting out,
もう別れるみたいなこと
言ってたな｡
so he was gonna break up with her.
てか 彼女いるのか？
いるよ 別の学校の３年｡
Wait, he has a girlfriend?
Sure does. A third-year at another school.
あと昔の彼女のことも
しょっちゅうﾎﾞﾛｸｿに言っててさ
He keeps bashing his exes, too.
こうはなりたくないなぁって
思う｡
I really hope I never end up like him.
貴重な情報ｻﾝｷｭ｡
That's just what I need. Thanks.
これで良心を痛めずに済む｡
Now I can do this with a clear conscience.
お お待たせ｡
S-Sorry to keep you waiting.
顔赤いぞ てか ５分遅刻｡
し しようがないじゃん
Why's your face so red?
And you're five minutes late.
Th-This is a date. I had to doll up.
準備とかあったし…｡
Doll up, huh?
準備ねぇ｡
まっ かわいいな｡
Well, you do look very cute.
か かわいいって言うな｡
D-Don't call me cute.
ﾐﾆｽｶｰﾄじゃないのは減点だけど
I'd usually dock points for no miniskirt, but I'll overlook it for the bare legs.
生足だから許す｡
足ばっか見るのも禁止！
Quit looking at my legs!
Oh, right.
あっそうだ ID｡
Gimme your chat ID.
少し遅れるって
連絡しようと思ったのに
I wanted to let you know I was running a bit late,
but you never told me what it was.
先輩のID 教えてもらってない｡
ないよ そんなの｡
え？
Ain't got one.
ｽﾏﾎもｹｰﾀｲも持ってない｡
何それ どういうこと!?
I don't have a cell phone.
Wait, what? I haven't an inklin' what you're talkin' about!
いっちょんわからん！
どうやって生きてるの？
How do you even live?!
Do people die if they don't have a cell phone?
ｽﾏﾎがないと 人は死ぬのか？
(朋絵)死ぬよ！
They do!
いきなりあくびか｡
あんまり寝てないの｡
Yawning already?
I didn't get much sleep.
Too excited for our date?
ﾃﾞｰﾄが楽しみで？
昨日の２時過ぎまで
I was chatting with the group until past 2 last night.
みんなでｸﾞﾙｰﾌﾟﾒｯｾｰｼﾞしてて｡
そのあと 動物のおもしろ動画
見てたら 朝になってた｡
Then I started watching funny animal videos, and it was morning before I knew it.
あと ﾃﾞｰﾄの予習をちょっと｡
さっさと寝ておけよ｡
Also, I had to practice for the date.
You should've just gone to sleep.
I can't go to bed while everyone else is still up!
みんな起きてるのに
私だけ寝るなんて無理！
動物のおもしろ動画は
暇なときでいいだろ｡
What about the funny animal videos?
Couldn't you have watched those later?
Everyone else said they'd watched them already.
みんな見たことあるって
言ってたし
話に入れないと困る｡
玲奈ちゃんのｵｽｽﾒなんだよ？
I had to watch them to keep up.
Rena-chan recommended them, y'know?
また玲奈ちゃんねぇ｡
あっそうだ 感想｡
Again with the Rena-chan?
Oh, I should tell them what I thought.
Your eyes look dead, Senpai.
先輩 目が死んでる｡
ふだんと同じだろ｡
They look the same as always to me.
So they always look dead?
じゃあ ふだんから死んでるんだ｡
Lastly, let's try diving in from the board over there.
≪最後は あちらの台から
飛び込みに挑戦してみましょう｡
(朋絵)あのﾍﾟﾝｷﾞﾝ
なんか先輩っぽい｡
That one penguin is kinda like you.
Are you that hyper one, then?
なら 古賀は あの元気なﾍﾟﾝｷﾞﾝ？
私は違う 後ろから
みんなについていってるﾍﾟﾝｷﾞﾝ｡
Nah, not that one.
I'm the one in the back that's following the rest.
お尻も大きいしな｡
まじめな話だったのに！
Yeah, it has a big butt too.
I was being serious there!
We did it!
≪やっと起きたようですね
ｼｮｰはもう終わりなんですが｡
Oh, he finally woke up.
The show's already over, though.
He doesn't care if people laugh at him.
みんなに笑われても平気で
ﾎﾝﾄ先輩そっくりじゃん｡
He really is just like you.
We also have a dolphin show,
so make sure to check it out as well.
ん？ どうした？
What's wrong?
You see...
あのね 中学まで
私 こんなんじゃなかったの｡
I wasn't like this during middle school.
Wow...
これは…｡
Plain Jane, much?
ｲﾓだな｡
だから見せたくなかったんじゃん｡
This is why I didn't wanna show you!
自分で見せといて？
お父さんの転勤で
Then why did you? I never asked.
My dad got transferred at work,
so we had to move here from Fukuoka.
福岡から こっちに
来ることになって…｡
ｸﾗｽでも目立たないｸﾞﾙｰﾌﾟにいたし
東京じゃ ださいって言われて
I used to be in a plain group in school.
I thought Tokyo folk would call me lame, not wanna be friends, and bully me.
友達なんかできなくて
絶対いじめられると思った｡
だから いろいろ研究したの｡
So I did my homework.
初めてﾒｰｸして
I put on makeup for the first time,
went to a fancy salon and changed my hairstyle,
おしゃれな美容院に行って
髪型変えて
服もﾌｧｯｼｮﾝ雑誌読んで真似して
言葉も特訓して…｡
and remade my wardrobe based on fashion mags.
I even practiced how to talk like people here.
そしたら こんなふうに
なっちゃった｡
That's how I turned into this.
気に入ってないのかよ 今の自分｡
Don't you like who you are now?
気に入ってる すごく好き｡
I do. I love myself.
だったら なに悩んでんだよ
うっとうしい｡
Then why rack your tiny little brain over it?
どうせ 思春期丸出しで
Are you being the typical teenager,
thinking this isn't the real you or whatever?
本当の自分は
こんなんじゃない とか
思ってるんだろ？
そ そうだけど…｡
Y-Yeah.
ｳｻﾞいわ｡
ひどっ！
What a pain.
Jerk!
It doesn't matter what you used to be.
What you are now is who you are.
前がどうだろうと
今のその姿が古賀だよ｡
きっかけはどうあれ
古賀は なろうと思って
Regardless of the reason, you chose to put in the effort to change, right?
努力して そうなったんだろ？
う うん｡
R-Right.
で 今の自分は
気に入ってるんだよな？
And you like who you are now, right?
それなのに
本当の自分じゃないとか
So why would you think this isn't the real you? That's just dumb.
そのほうがどうかしてるって｡
なんか悔しい｡
I feel like you just played me, and I don't like it.
先輩に言いくるめられたみたいで｡
行くぞ ほら 次は江の島だろ｡
Let's get going.
Next up is Enoshima, right?
Yeah.
知り合い？
ｸﾗｽﾒｲﾄの米山さん｡
You know her?
That's Yoneyama-san, my classmate.
(朋絵)米山さ～ん！
Yoneyama-san!
(米山)古賀さん…｡
Koga-san?
A-And the second-year who went
full circle to dateable?
それに １周回ってｱﾘの先輩｡
それ ﾎﾝﾄに浸透してるのな｡
That's actually a thing, huh?
I-I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい｡
何か探してるの？
Searching for something?
う うん…｡
私も一緒に探すよ｡
Y-Yeah.
I'll help look.
い いいよ 古賀さんは
香芝さんのｸﾞﾙｰﾌﾟだし｡
I-It's fine. You're in Kashiba-san's group.
３人で探したほうが早いだろ｡
先輩も こう言ってるし｡
Three pairs of eyes is better than one.
Senpai says he wants to help too.
うん… ｽﾄﾗｯﾌﾟなの｡
Thanks.
It's a phone strap.
My friends and I got matching ones.
今の友達と お揃いにしたやつ
ｸﾗｹﾞの人形がついてて…｡
It has a jellyfish on it.
このへんに落としたのは
間違いないのか？
Are you sure you lost it around here?
す すみません
それもわかりません｡
S-Sorry. I don't know.
謝らなくていいよ｡
No need to apologize.
(朋絵)先輩はﾍﾝな人だけど
怖くはないから｡
He might be a weirdo, but he's not scary.
(米山)うん…｡
あれじゃないか？
Okay.
Wait, is that it?
あっ うわぁ！
あっ 待て！
Hey, wait.
古賀さん…｡
わわわ… やった！
Koga-san!
Got it!
あっ うわぁ！
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
June 30th
風邪ひいたか？
先輩…｡
Catch a cold?
Senpai?
玲奈ちゃんから聞いた｡
全然平気｡
Rena-chan told me.
I'm fine.
みかんの缶詰 食うか？
Want some canned tangerines?
途中で 学校の外 出るの
校則違反だよ｡
It's against the rules to leave during school hours, y'know?
じゃあ いらないな｡
食べる…｡
Don't want it, then?
I'll take it.
あ～んのほうがよければ
してやろうか｡
If you like, I can feed you.
食べにくいからいい｡
That'd make it hard to eat, so no thanks.
ねぇ 先輩 なんで 私の
むちゃなお願い聞いてくれたの？
Hey, Senpai. Why'd you agree to my crazy request?
古賀が必死に頼んできたからだよ｡
Because you looked like you really needed help.
私のこと ほとんど知らないのに？
But you barely even knew me.
Hey, we were butt-kicking buddies.
尻を蹴り合った仲だろ｡
もう まじめに聞いてるのに｡
Jeez, I'm asking a serious question here!
でも あのとき 古賀は
いいやつだと思った｡
But that incident did make me think you were a nice girl.
あとは ぶっちゃけ
かわいいから｡
Also, frankly, it was because you're cute.
またふざける｡
古賀が ぶさいくだったら
Still not a straight answer.
I don't know if I would've done the same if you were ugly.
同じふうにしてたか わからない｡
男なんて そんなもんだ｡
してたよ 先輩は｡
That's how guys are wired.
Don't worry. You would have.
風邪なら休めばよかったのに｡
You should've taken the day off if you were sick.
休んだら みんなの話に
ついていけなくなるもん｡
If I had, I wouldn't be able to keep up with the others.
１日くらいで？
その１日が命とりなの｡
It's just one day.
And missing one day can prove fatal.
保健室で寝てたら一緒だろ｡
今も保健室にいること
What's the difference if you're spending it in the infirmary?
I'm actually worried about what the people in class are thinking about this too.
教室のみんなに
どう思われてるのか
気になってる｡
自意識過剰だな 古賀って｡
You're way too self-conscious.
先輩がおかしいんだよ｡
みんなにﾍﾝな目で見られたり
No, you're the weird one here!
How are you fine with being the outcast, the laughing stock of the entire school?
笑いものにされたりして
どうして平気なの？
べつに 全人類に好かれるために
生きてるわけじゃないし｡
It's not like my sole purpose in life is to make all of mankind love me.
私は みんなに好かれたい｡
Well, I want everyone to like me.
ってか 嫌われたくない｡
Or at least, I don't wanna be hated.
僕は たった一人でもいいけどね｡
I'd be fine with just one pillar of support.
世界中に嫌われたとしても
Even if the whole world hates me, as long as that one person needs me, I can keep trucking.
その一人が必要としてくれたら
生きていける｡
Teenage Pig Doesn't
Dream of Bunny Girls
Here. To thank you for the day before yesterday.
はい これ おとといのお返し｡
なぜ桃缶？
Why canned peach?
桃尻だけに？
変態禁止！
Peach emoji?
Don't be a perv!
I'll think of this as you and relish it tonight.
今夜は これを古賀だと思って
おいしくいただくかな｡
ｱ ｱﾎｰ！ 言っとくけど 私
D-Dumbass!
Just so you know, my butt isn't that big!
そこまで
お尻大きくないからね！
Oh, please. No need to be humble.
またまた ご謙遜を｡
その返し おかしい！
That comeback makes no sense!
Say, how did things go with
Sakurajima-senpai, anyway?
先輩さ 桜島先輩とは
結局 どうだったの？
返事待ち｡
えっ まだふられてないの？
Waiting for her answer.
Huh? She hasn't rejected you?
If it hadn't been for that loop,
例のﾙｰﾌﾟ現象が起こってなければ
あの日の昼休みに
she would've agreed to go out with me
at lunch break that day.
おつきあいのｵｯｹｰ
もらえてたんだよ｡
ｳｿ～｡
ﾎﾝﾄだって｡
Lies.
It's the truth.
I don't buy it.
絶対ｳｿだ だって桜島先輩だよ？
芸能人だよ？
I mean, it's Sakurajima-senpai. She's a celeb.
桜島先輩から
好きって言われたの？
Has she told you that she likes you?
Well... I guess she hasn't.
それは… 言われてない｡
See? You just got the wrong idea!
ほら～ 先輩の気のせいだって｡
次に告白するときは
I'll try my best to make her say it
the next time I ask her out.
そう言ってもらえるように
努力するよ｡
麻衣さん どうしたの？
Mai-san? What's up?
[℡]咲太が 私の声を
聞きたいんじゃないかと思って
I called because I figured you'd want to hear my voice.
電話してあげたの｡
まさに今
I was just thinking about you, actually.
麻衣さんのこと考えてた｡
[℡]ﾊﾟﾝﾂ履いてるんでしょうね？
I hope your underwear's on.
[℡]咲太が 私で
そういうことするのは
Of course, I understand that you'd fantasize about me, but...
仕方ないけど｡
全裸です！
I'm butt naked!
P-Perv!
へ 変態！
[℡]ｳｿです｡
I'm kidding. I just got out of the bath,
but I'm wearing that much at least.
風呂上がりだけど
ﾊﾟﾝﾂだけ履いてます｡
つまんないｳｿつかないの｡
Don't tell such stupid lies.
On nights when I cannot sleep,
I may turn to you for assistance.
悶々として眠れない夜は
麻衣さんの
お世話になるかもしれません｡
Yeah, yeah. Feel free.
[℡]はいはい 好きにしたら｡
それより そっちはどう？
Anyway, how have you been?
[℡]かわいい彼女とのﾃﾞｰﾄは
楽しかった？
Did you have fun on the date with your cute girlfriend?
Yeah, more or less.
まぁ それなりに｡
へぇ｡
Oh?
[℡]今の質問 なんと答えるのが
正解なんですか？
How was I supposed to answer that question?
今すぐ家を飛び出して
鹿児島に会いにきてくれるとか｡
"I'll leave home at once and come see you in Kagoshima," or something?
[℡]で 全裸で
抱きしめればいいんですか？
And then what? I hug you butt naked?
That would weird me out.
それは引く｡
麻衣さん 撮影は楽しいですか？
Mai-san, is the shoot fun?
楽しいわよ
咲太は やりたい仕事ないの？
It is.
Do you have an ideal profession?
Well, I'd like to be Santa Claus in the future.
まっ 将来は
ｻﾝﾀｸﾛｰｽになりたいかな｡
[℡]年364日も休みだからでしょ？
ﾊﾞﾚたか｡
Because you'd have 364 days off in a year, right?
Busted, huh?
[℡]ﾊﾞｶ言ってると ﾊﾞｶになるわよ｡
Keep talking stupid and you really will turn stupid.
July 5th
Futaba.
双葉 よっ！
Yo.
Kunimi...
(理央)国見…｡
何か用？
You need something?
I was wondering if Sakuta was here.
He wasn't in his classroom.
咲太 来てないかって思って｡
教室にいなかったからさ｡
例の１年生のところじゃない？
あ～ そっちか｡
He's probably gone to see that first-year.
Oh, right. There was her.
梓川が来たら伝言しておくけど｡
Want me to pass on a message if he comes here?
Futaba, you in?
双葉 いるか？
悪い 邪魔した｡
Sorry for interrupting.
梓川はﾊﾞｶか ﾊﾞｶなのか！
私にﾍﾝな気をつかうな！
Are you stupid? Are you?!
Don't try to give us alone time!
Kunimi will find out!
国見に気づかれる！
If that was all it took,
I'm pretty sure he'd know by now.
このくらいで気づくなら
あいつ もう気づいてると思うぞ｡
双葉の気持ちに｡
How you feel, I mean.
That would suck.
それは… 困る｡
なんか取り込み中みたいだから
また今度な 咲太｡
You seem busy, so I'll catch you some other time, Sakuta.
相変わらずｲｹﾒﾝなやつだな｡
He's always so handsome.
で ｲｹﾒﾝじゃない ﾌﾞﾀ野郎の梓川は
何をしに来たわけ？
So, what brings the decidedly un-handsome pig here?
Oh, well... There hasn't been any more looping since that day,
ああ あれ以来 同じ日の
繰り返しは 起こらないから
結局 何だったのかと思ってさ｡
so I was wondering what that was all about in the end.
なら 梓川が
言ってたとおりなんじゃないの？
It's probably exactly what you said, then.
今 梓川の恋人ってことに
なっている 例の１年生が
That first-year who's now your pretend girlfriend was Laplace's demon,
ﾗﾌﾟﾗｽの悪魔｡
自分の都合のいい未来が出るまで
ｻｲｺﾛを振り続けていた｡
and she kept rolling the dice
until she found a positive future.
で 今は満足のいく状態だから
Now...
She's satisfied with the present outcome,
so she doesn't feel the need to reroll.
やり直す必要はないというわけ｡
本人は自覚なしだけどな｡
She herself doesn't seem aware of it, though.
(理央)自覚してたら
本物の悪魔かもね｡
If she were, she'd be a real demon.
Kamisato?
上里｡
(沙希)私 前にも言ったよね
佑真に近づかないでって｡
Didn't I tell you to stay away from Yuuma?
僕が聞いたのは ｢しゃべんないで｣
だったと思うけど｡
I'm pretty sure I heard "stop talking to him."
同じことでしょ！ あと
あの物理実験室の女は何？
Same difference.
Also...
Who's that girl in the physics lab?
佑真と どういう関係？
よく話してるけど｡
What's with her and Yuuma?
I see them talking a lot.
国見に聞けよ｡
梓川も仲いいんでしょ？
Ask Kunimi, not me.
You're friends with her too,
aren't you? Just answer me!
いいから答えて！
なんだよ ｶﾘｶﾘして｡
Why so butthurt? Are you constipated?
便秘か？
死ね！
Die! Just drop dead!
今すぐ死ね！
もうﾎﾝﾄ最低！
I can't believe you!
食物繊維 摂れよ｡
Try to eat more fiber!
July 6th
国見 面倒だから 先に言っとく｡
Kunimi, this is getting annoying,
so I'm just gonna come out and say it.
昨日 またお前の彼女に絡まれた｡
そりゃ 災難だったな｡
Your girlfriend came snapping at me again yesterday.
That must've sucked.
もう僕か彼女か どっちかにしろ｡
It's me or her now. Choose.
なんだよ その究極になってない
究極の選択｡
You make it sound like a hard choice, but there's only one option there.
わかった 今晩 電話しとくわ｡
Fine. I'll call her tonight.
頼むぞ ﾎﾝﾄ｡
で 咲太
Please.
Anyway, Sakuta,
古賀さんと つきあってるってﾏｼﾞ？
is it true you're going out with Koga-san?
ﾏｼﾞだな｡
ﾏｼﾞか！
It's true.
For real?
実は まだ
お試し期間って感じだけど｡
Actually, it's more like a trial period right now.
だったら やっぱ 昨日のうちに
言っとけばよかったな｡
Then I should've just told you yesterday.
は？
古賀さんだけどさ…｡
About Koga-san...
なんだよ｡
よくないうわさが流れてる｡
What?
There are some ugly rumors floating around,
させ子だとか ﾋﾞｯﾁだとか｡
calling her an easy slut and stuff.
咲太と やりまくってるとかね｡
なんだ そりゃ｡
And how you two are going at it like rabbits.
What the heck?
俺も部活のｸﾞﾙｰﾌﾟﾒｯｾｰｼﾞで
知ったんだけどさ｡
I only heard it through the
basketball team's group chat.
咲太 前に陽介先輩のこと
聞いたよな？
Didn't you ask about Yousuke-senpai before?
Futaba, do you ever think about things you could've done differently?
双葉さ もし あのとき… って
考えること ないか？
梓川にとっては妹さんのこと？
そうだよ 悪いか？
For you, would it be the thing with your sister?
Yeah. Is that so wrong?
悪くはないけど
梓川らしくはないかもね｡
Not really, but it isn't like you.
べつに 本当にやり直したいと
思ってるわけじゃない｡
It's not like I really want to go back in time or anything.
もしも… なんて
考えても仕方ないことを
I just want to make sure that I don't have any dumb regrets in the future.
考えなくて済むように
したいだけだよ｡
なるほど 梓川らしいね｡
I see. Now that's more like you.
あのさ 双葉｡
何？
Say, Futaba.
What?
運動部で鍛えてるうえに
自分より体のでかいやつに
Do you think there's any way a guy could beat an athlete who's bigger than him?
勝てる方法って あると思うか？
さあね
人間は猿じゃないんだから
Well, people aren't monkeys.
頭を使えば勝てるんじゃない？
He could beat him by using his head.
[ﾃｰﾌ]桜島麻衣です｡
This is Sakurajima Mai.
[ﾃｰﾌ]先ほど鹿児島から戻りました｡
一応 報告しておきます｡
I'm calling to let you know that I've just returned from Kagoshima.
July 7th
(亜矢)前髪失敗しちゃってさ
もうﾔﾊﾞくない？
I messed up my bangs! This looks so bad!
Quit looking so gloomy.
辛気くさい顔するな｡
先輩…｡
≪やりまくってるらしいぜ｡
Senpai.
I hear they're going at it like rabbits.
(前沢)最近の１年は お盛んだな｡
First-years these days sure have big appetites.
ﾌｯ…｡
Huh? Did you just sneer at me?
は？ 今 笑ったよな？
まだ笑ってますけど 何か？
I'm still sneering at you. What about it?
ふざけてんのか！
いえ ﾊﾞｶにしてるだけです｡
You messing with me?
Not at all. I'm just mocking you.
Senpai!
先輩！
Oh? You wanna go?
お？ やんのか？
うっ… お前 卑怯だろ！
Dude, that's dirty!
それは ｱﾝﾀだろ！
うっ…｡
Right back at you!
ﾀﾞｻｯ！
誰がだ！
Lame.
Who is?!
顔 洗ったほうがいいですよ｡
はぁ？
You should probably wash your face.
昨日 ｳﾝｺ踏んだので｡
I stepped on some poop yesterday.
ふ ふざけんな！
ふざけてるのは そっちでしょ｡
You think this is funny?!
I don't know, do you?
自分が見世物にされるのが嫌なら
ｱﾎなことするな｡
If you don't like being embarrassed,
then maybe stop doing stupid things.
生き方がﾀﾞｻすぎる｡
The way you live your life is hella lame.
先輩 もういい｡
Senpai, that's enough.
いいや これだけは
言わせてもらう｡
No. I have to put this out there.
やりまくってる？ 冗談じゃない｡
Going at it like rabbits? Are you freaking kidding me?
僕は… 童貞だ！
I'm a virgin!
Se—Hey, wait—
ちょっ… せ 先輩 やりすぎ！
You went too far, Senpai!
知るか｡
絶対やりすぎ！
Like I care!
You definitely went too far!
前に先輩が言ってたこと
少しわかったかも｡
I think I understand what you were talking about the other day.
ん？
世界中が敵でも
Y'know, "even if the whole world hates me,
as long as that one person needs me," blah blah.
１人だけ必要としてくれたら…
的なやつ｡
的なってな…
ちゃんと覚えとけよ｡
What do you mean, "blah blah"?
You should remember my pearls of wisdom.
ﾎﾝﾄに彼女って感じだった｡
I really felt like your girlfriend back there.
大事にされてる感じだった｡
I felt loved.
１学期は そうする約束だから｡
Well, I did agree to be your boyfriend until the end of first term.
普通 ｳｿの恋人に
あそこまでしないよ｡
Who goes that far for a pretend girlfriend?
僕は完璧主義だからさ｡
なにそれ しけと～｡
I happen to be a perfectionist.
What the heck? That's so square.
なんだ それ？
先輩 そがんことも知らんとね｡
Say what?
Ya don't even know that? It means lame.
つまんないって意味｡
(受信音)
あっ 玲奈ちゃんから｡
Oh, it's from Rena-chan.
ﾌｯ ｢前沢先輩には幻滅｣だって｡
She says she's lost her hots for Maesawa-senpai.
顔にｳﾝｺがついたくらいで
冷めるなら
If a little poop on his face was enough to kill it,
then it wasn't much of a crush.
その程度の
憧れだったってことか｡
あっ そだ 先輩
１つ言っておきたいんだけど｡
Oh right, Senpai. I need to get something out of the way.
ﾄｲﾚか？
違う！
Washroom?
No!
私 その… したことないから｡
I-I've, uh...
never done it.
何を？
Never done what?
私 処女だからね！
I'm a virgin, okay?!
Don't laugh, you meanie!
笑うとか ひどくない？
僕が あんなうわさを
信じてると思ったか｡
Did you really think I believed those rumors?
思わないけど…｡
No, but I'd hate it if you did.
信じてたら やだなって…｡
でも 古賀って 彼氏いたこと
あるんじゃなかったっけ？
Didn't you have a boyfriend before, though?
だって みんな 中学のときに
いたって言うから｡
My friends all said they had one in middle school,
なんか ｢朋絵もいたよね｣的な
感じで…｡
so when they asked me, I said I had one too.
なるほどね｡
それに
Ah, I see.
Besides, I thought you'd look down on me
if I said I'd never dated anyone before.
つきあったことないなんて
言ったら
先輩に なめられると思って｡
古賀は 何と戦ってんだよ｡
What are you even fighting in life?
わかんない｡
No idea.
あのさ 先輩…｡
あ？
Hey, Senpai.
私 先輩に どうやって
恩返しすればいい？
How can I ever repay you?
じゃ ｳｿが終わったら
友達になってくれ｡
Be my friend after we're done with this lie, then.
あっ…｡
嫌なら いいぞ｡
It's fine if you don't want to.
Nah.
しようがないから
親友になってあげる｡
I'll become your best friend,
since you won't find anyone else.
Equipped my cat with a hero's sword. Too cute, I'm dead
seconds until you can skip this ad
That's my Sakuta-san. A total pig.
Next Episode
#6: This World You Chose